Contact

wahyu.teri@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tri-wahyu-prasetyo-84ba90b2 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Project Management Front-end Development JavaScript

Tri Wahyu Prasetyo

Frontend Web Programmer

Malang Area, East Java, Indonesia

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Management, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Teknik Informatika from University of Brawijaya.

Experience

PT.Visionet Data Internasional Programmer January 2018 - January 2020 (2 years 1 month)

PT ITPI Technology Web Programmer May 2017 - August 2017 (4 months)

Interaktif Media Informatika Frontend Web Developer July 2015 - September 2015 (3 months) Yogyakarta Area, Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Education

University of Brawijaya
Bachelor's degree, Teknik Informatika · (2012 - 2017)